https://www.active.com/privacy-settings

Find Camps & Activities for your Active Kids
Infants (0-1)
Toddlers (2-4)
Big Kids (5-8)
Tweens (9-12)
Teens (13-18)
Find Camps & Activities for your Active Kids
Infants (0-1)
Toddlers (2-4)
Big Kids (5-8)
Tweens (9-12)
Teens (13-18)
Shop
Need Help?
Event Organizers
ACTIVE WORKS®
From marketing exposure to actionable data
insights, ACTIVE Works® is the race management
software for managing & marketing your events.
Learn More
Customer Login
Privacy, Transparency and Trust
Privacy, Transparency, and Trust
Trust is the cornerstone of a great brand and respecting the privacy rights of our customers is an integral part of building that trust. You have the right to manage your personal information.
Our Commitment
A Letter from our Chief Data Officer
Read the blog post
Our Mission
ACTIVE Aspires to Make the World a Better Place
Read the blog post
My Wallet
Your payment information is securely stored. View or update your payment information.
View more
Newsletters & Marketing Emails
View and update your ACTIVE newsletter subscriptions and marketing preferences.
Edit preferences
Request a Copy of Your Personal Information
Submit a request to receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you.
Access your data
Cookie Settings
Review and update your cookie preferences.
Edit preferences
Delete Your Account and Personal Information
Permanently deactivate your account and associated personal information. You will not be able retrieve or reactivate your account or personal information.
Delete your data
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
Some state laws (like the CCPA) may consider sharing personal information for targeted advertising purposes a “sale.” Click here to modify your preferences and opt-out of the use of your personal information for targeted advertising purposes.
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
Finding a virtualactivity is now easier!
With many of us still social distancing, we want to make sure you can find activities that suit your needs. There are lots of virtual options to keep you active and engaged — just select “Virtual Activities” as your location, and you’re ready to go.
Find a virtual activity
Adding family members helps ACTIVE find events specific to your family's interests.
Look for this banner for recommended activities.
Are you sure you want to delete this family member?
© 2020 Active Network, LLC and/or its affiliates and licensors. All rights reserved.
